iahgames.com 2016-05-15

# IAHGames

Our goal is to maintain your trust and confidence when handling personal information about you. We have adopted an on-Line Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us. This Privacy Policy details how IAH safeguards the privacy of our online visitors and does not apply to information that may be collected by IAH offline. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply when you link to other sites from an IAH website as we cannot control the activities on those other sites. This Privacy Policy will tell you:

What personal identifying information we may collect

What other types of information we may collect

How your personal information may be used

Who is collecting your information

With whom may your personal information be shared?

What choices you have regarding the collection, use, and distribution of your personal information

What cookies are and how we use them

What are Internet Protocol addresses

How secure your personal information is

What to do if you want to correct or review your personal information

What to do if you have a question or complaint

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our privacy policy statement or policies, please contact our Privacy Policy Administrator at [privacy@iahgames.com](mailto:privacy@iahgames.com)

What personal information is collected?

IAHGames will only collect personal information on a voluntary basis. If an on-line visitor submits information to IAH, it will usually take the form of any of the following:

  * Product registration or registration for on-line game participation,
  * Forums / message boards,
  * Contest registrations,
  * Consumer feedback
  * Surveys, and/or newsletters.
  * IAH promotional materials

Personal information collected may include your name, home address, phone number, NRIC / identity card and/or e-mail address. We do not require this information to use our products or gain access to our sites, however, you will not be able to utilize certain features that require registration or receive materials such as newsletters unless such information is provided.

BACK TO TOP

What other types of information may we collect?

For some activities, we may ask you to create a username and password and/or to provide other, non-personal information such as your age, date of birth, gender, and/or game and platform preferences; and, combine such information with your personal information. In addition, your web browser or client software may transmit certain geographic information or information regarding your computer (capabilities, etc.) to IAH. IAH may use this information to generate aggregate statistics about our user community and may provide such information to advertisers and/or our partners. In addition, IAH may use such information for security, system integrity (the prevention of hacking, cheats, etc.), or enforcement purposes.

BACK TO TOP

How do we use your personal information?

The personal information you provide IAH will allow us to fulfill your product or service; alert you of new products or services, features, or enhancements; handle/route your customer service questions or issues; and/or notify you of upgrade opportunities, contests, promotions, or special events and offers. IAH may enhance or merge the personal information collected at an IAH site with data from third parties. IAH may also provide your personal information to other companies or organizations that offer products or services that may be of interest to you. In such cases, we will notify you that the information will be shared and provide you with an opportunity to opt-out.

Lastly, we may use your personal information for internal marketing, profiling, or demographic purposes, so we can adapt our products and services to better suit your needs. We do this to better understand and serve our customers.

Please be advised that personal information submitted by individuals acting solely in a business capacity (e.g., personal information contained in job applicant's resume) is not subject to the uses set forth above or to any other practices stated in this Privacy Policy.

BACK TO TOP

Who is collecting your information?

When you are asked for information while on a IAH site, you are sharing that information with IAH, its parent, and its various affiliates and partner companies, unless specifically stated otherwise. As a result of this sharing, you may receive communications from any of IAH's affiliates. In addition, some services are provided in conjunction with partner companies. If your personal information is being collected by another company other than IAH, you will be notified at the time the information is collected. We will ask if you want us to share with third parties your name, mailing address, and email address. Should you wish not to share such information, you may click 'No' in the box at the time you register as a member, or each time such information is requested.

Please be aware that we cannot control the activities of third parties to whom we provide data, and as such we cannot guarantee that they adhere to the same privacy and security procedures as IAH.

However, if disclosure to third parties is required, we have the option of requiring these entities to not use your personal information for any other purpose (other than to fulfill product orders etc.), and that they have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the information they obtain from us. Please be aware that advertisers or websites with links to our sites may collect personal information about you. Please also be reminded that this Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, those other advertisers or websites.

BACK TO TOP

With whom may your personal information be shared?

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you if you are violating the Terms of Service or Use Agreements for a IAH site or product, or may be causing injury to or interference (intentionally or unintentionally) with IAH's rights or property, other users of a IAH site or product, or anyone else who could be harmed by your activities.

As with any business, your personal information is also an asset of IAH and will become part of our normal business records. As such, we may also disclose your personal information to a third party if we decide to sell a line of business to that third party, so you can continue to receive service and information in connection with that line of business with as little disruption as possible. Similarly, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, your personal information may be transferred to IAH 's successor or assign.

IAH sites may also have message boards and/or chat areas, where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board or chat area, please be aware that the information is being made publicly available on-line and the user does so at his or her own risk.

BACK TO TOP

What choices do I have regarding the collection, use, and distribution of my personal information?

IAH allows you to control the way that we use personal identifying information that we might obtain. At the time you provide personal information, IAH may give you the option of declining any future offers or information about new products, promotions, or services. In addition, many of the "mailings" IAH may send you, such as newsletters, have procedures within them to cancel the receipt of any future mailings.

Subject to security and privacy concerns, (e.g. regarding your password and credit card number), IAH will give you the ability to review, correct, delete, and/or update your information. To do so, you may send us an email at[privacy@iahgames.com](mailto:privacy@iahgames.com)

At the time you are asked for your information, we will inform you of the following:

  * The personally identifiable information to be shared;
  * The identity of the third party; and
  * A link to the third party's privacy statement, if available.

Note to parents

We recognize a special obligation to protect personal information about young children. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 12. We take children's privacy seriously and encourage parents to play an active role in their children's online experience at all times. As such, we urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses, or phone numbers, without permission, when on-line. Teenagers under the age of 17 and over the age of 12 should encourage their parents to review this policy and to contact us if they would like to evoke our opt-out policy or to raise any concerns. For children between the ages of 13-18, they should get permission from their parents before posting anything personal and identifiable on the message boards. They should also not tell anyone online anything private about themselves.

BACK TO TOP

What are cookies and how do you use them?

Cookies are a feature of your Web browser that allows Web sites to transfer bits of information to your computer for record-keeping purposes. A cookie stored on your computer can be used to "remember" things like your password, or that you have already registered. This allows us to speed up your future activities, saving the time you would normally spend entering information such as your password or registration. In addition, IAH may use cookies to retrieve user information for promotional, marketing, or security purposes.

BACK TO TOP

What are Internet protocol addresses?

An Internet protocol ("IP") address is the unique number assigned to your server or Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). IAH may track such IP addresses for system administration, to report aggregate information, site tracking, or to prevent our servers from being abused.

BACK TO TOP

How secure is my personal information?

IAH has taken steps to assure that all information collected will remain secure and in its original form, i.e. free from any alteration. As such, access to all personal information is strictly controlled. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. When credit card information is transmitted, for example, we use industry standard, SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of personal information.

BACK TO TOP

What if I have a question, complaint or wish to update my personal information?

If you wish to update your personal information, have any questions or wish to file a complaint, please feel free to e-mail us at[privacy@iahgames.com](mailto:privacy@iahgames.com)

BACK TO TOP

By using this Website, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the change on this website or in this Privacy Policy and, if necessary, give you additional choices regarding such change. Your continued use of the IAH website will signify your acceptance of these changes.
